gravitydefyer.com 2009-04-14

# See how your information is safe with our privacy policy

**Privacy Policy**

Your personal information is confidential. Here's what we collect and how we use it: * We do not rent, sell or exchange e-mail addresses. 

  * When you place an order with GravityDefyer.com we collect your name, address, telephone number, credit card information and your e-mail address. We use this information to fulfill your order and to communicate with you about your order. Placing an order will automatically set up your account with GravityDefyer.com. If you're a registered customer, you enter your billing and shipping information only once each time you shop and you can also access your Order History to review information about past online purchases. You can review or revise your personal information at any time.
  * After ordering from GravityDefyer.com, we may also send you our print catalogs. If you are a print catalog customer, we may at times share your information with our carefully selected partners. If you do not wish to receive a printed catalog or if you do not want GravityDefyer.com to share your postal information with our catalog partners, please e-mail your specific request to: InfoCenter@GravityDefyer.com or call 1-800-429-1139.
  * When you subscribe to our Gadget Alert, we collect your name and e-mail address so that we can send you advance notice of sales and events or tell you about new products and services. You can unsubscribe from our Gadget Alert at any time by sending your unsubscribe request to: InfoCenter@GravityDefyer.com and type "unsubscribe" in the subject line.
  * When you enter a sweepstakes on GravityDefyer.com or any other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so that we can administer the sweepstakes and notify the winners. You may also subscribe to our Gadget Alert when entering a sweepstakes.
  * When you visit our site, our web server automatically recognizes only your domain name, but not your e-mail address. We collect the domain name and monitor general site use and traffic patterns to improve our web site and the products and services we offer. The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded. We may use collected data to customize the content and/or layout of our pages for each individual visitor.
  * If elements of our privacy policy change, we will post the policy changes to our web site. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
  * We contract with an Ad Server partner to advertise GravityDefyer.com on various web sites. As a result of your accessing our site through one of these advertisements, the ad server company may collect information such as your domain type or your IP address information.
  * Our current technology platform requires that your browser be set to accept cookies. Cookies are bits of electronic information that a website can transfer to your computer's hard drive in order to make online shopping easier and quicker. We do not store personal information such as your name or phone number in your cookie. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many major websites use them.
